https://www.robinsoninc.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Robinson Values Your PrivacyPRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy (“Policy”) shall govern and apply to anyone accessing or using the websites located at robinsonmetal.com, or any other website controlled by Robinson, Inc. (“Robinson”) (collectively, “Website”), in email, text, and any other electronic messages between you and Robinson, and at any other websites controlled by Robinson.  Throughout the Website, the terms “we”, “us”, and “our” refer to Robinson.  This Policy summarizes what personally identifiable information Robinson may collect, and how Robinson might use this information.  This Policy also describes important topics relating to your privacy.Please read this Policy carefully to understand Robinson’s policies and practices regarding your information and how Robinson will treat it.  If you do not agree with the provisions set forth in this Policy, your choice is not to use the Website.  This Policy may change from time to time.  Your continued use of the Website after Robinson makes changes to the Policy is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the Policy periodically for updates.What Information Do We Collect?Robinson has access to/collects information that you voluntarily provide via the Website, email correspondence, or via other direct contact from you.  We will only collect the personally identifiable information (such as, but not limited to, name, title, company name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) provided by you and with your consent.  Robinson collects cookies on the website to track user activity on the website to better understand user’s needs.Why Do We Collect Your Personal Information?Robinson offers various products and services to its customers.  We strive to provide customers the utmost quality and best possible experience.  We use your voluntarily provided personal information to both meet those expectations and to raise yours, through internal uses such as analyzing customer preferences and improving product availability.How Does We Use Your Information?Robinson is the sole owner of the information collected on the Website.  We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.  We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us.  We may use any information we collect from you to improve the Website, improve customer service, or process transactions.We will not share your information with any third party outside of its organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request (e.g. to ship an order or send your requested information).  We retain the right to transfer necessary information in connection with the sale of its business.  Only if you affirmatively opt-in will we contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products, or services.  You may opt out of any email newsletter or specials at any time.Your Access To And Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.  You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on the Website:See what data we have about you, if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data.You have the right to access the personal information you provided to us.  If you require details of your personal information, we will need to verify your identity before meeting your request, which we will process in a reasonable time.  If you find that the information we hold about you is inaccurate or out of date, we will promptly correct it upon receipt of the requested changes from you.We strive to adhere to standards required by a data controller under the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation.How Do We Protect Your Information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.  Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to a secure third-party processing site.  No credit card information is stored on the site.  While Robinson uses encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, Robinson also protects your information offline.  Robinson grants access to personally identifiable information only to employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service). The computers/servers in which Robinson stores personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.Children’s Use Of The WebsiteThe Website is intended for users who are 13 years of age and older.  If you are under the age of 13, you are not permitted to submit any personal information to the Website.  The Website is not directed to children under 13, and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13.  We will promptly delete any personal information from a person under the age of 13 should we discover that it has collected such information from a person under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent.Your ConsentBy using the Website, you consent to Robinson’s online Policy.If you feel that we are not abiding by this Policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-920-494-7411, via customerservice@robinsoninc.com, or via the Contact page on the Website.
When you partner with Robinson you can expect:
Expertise
30% of our team has been at Robinson over 10 years
Relationships
25% long term customers (15+ years)
Project Management
One point of contact with dedicated estimating and routing team
End to End Solutions
From concept to completion
Have a project in mind?Let’s Talk!
Modular conveyor options offer temporary and permanent solutions
December 8, 2020
Read More »
Industrial process piping requires adherence to strict standards
December 1, 2020
Read More »
Lane diverter technology enhances product handling efficiency
November 10, 2020
Read More »
Food industry fabrication helps create a safe working environment
November 3, 2020
Read More »
Robinson’s sanitary conveyors help industrial customers stay clean
October 13, 2020
Read More »
